activemeter.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy for our Industrial Online Marketing System

Everyone at ActiveConversion is committed to protecting your privacy. This ActiveConversion Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices and how they apply to our Website and our Subscription Service. This Privacy Policy governs how we collect, use, process and share information relating to individuals (“Personal Information”), and your rights and choices regarding use, access, and correction of your personal information.

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@activeconversion.com](mailto:privacy@activeconversion.com).

  1. Information We Collect
  2. How We Use the Information
  3. International Transfer of Information
  4. How to Access and Control Your Personal Information

****1\. Information We Collect****

* * *

**Information We Collect Directly From You**

When visiting our website or using our Subscription Services, we may require you to provide your Personal Information such as name, email, phone number, job title, company name and mailing address. This is common information that would normally be on a business card and in the public domain.

**Information We Collect From Other Sources**

We may collect information about you from other sources, including our partners, and combine this information with the Personal Information provided by you. This helps us update our records, identify new customers, create tailored advertising, and analyze overall trends so we may facilitate and provide relevant content, event promotions, and services that may be of interest to you.

**Log Data**

When you use our subscription services or view content provided by us or customers of our subscription services, we automatically collect information about your hardware and software. This information can include IP address, your internet service provider (ISP), the operating system, browser type, domain names, referring domains, files viewed on the site, and access times and duration on the site. This information is used by ActiveConversion for the operations of the Subscription Service to provide general statistics on the use of the website in service and for maintaining the quality of the Subscription Service.

**Cookies & Related Technologies**

We use cookies and similar technologies such as tags and Javascript to compile information about the usage of our website and websites using our Subscription Services. 

When you visit our website or a website using our Subscription Services, we may place a cookie on your browser, which can collect log data, Personal Information voluntarily submitted by you, and your online activities over time and across different sites. The use of cookies allows us to analyze the overall behaviour, determine areas of interest to better deliver relevant content and increase overall visitor experience.  Third-party vendors, including Google, may also implement cookies in order to support remarketing campaigns in Google AdWords.

****2\. How We Use The Information****

* * *

We process and analyze information such as log data to analyze the behaviour and preference of visitors in order to improve the quality of the content, product, and services we provide. Customers of our Subscription Services utilize the analytical data in a similar manner to offer an enriched experience to their potential customers.

We sometimes use this information for remarketing to reach people who have previously shown interest in our services. We connect to potential customers while they’re online by showing a compelling message or offer that may encourage them to return. Third party vendors, such as Google, help us target potential clients by placing ads on the Google Display Network. Ad placement is done by using cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to your website. If visitors would like to opt-out of Google’s use of cookies, they can do so by visiting Google’s [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). Alternatively, they can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**ActiveConversion Partners**

From time to time, we may share your information with trusted partners for such things as streamlining registration of co-marketing events that are permitted by you. We work with partners and agents to provide services to visitors to our website, our customers, and users of our Subscription Services that may need to share your information with them to provide the support, products or services to you. In all cases where we share your information, we require the partner and/or agent to adhere to this Privacy Policy.

****3\. How to Access and Control Your Personal Information****

* * *

Your rights to your Personal Information, subject to local data production laws:

  * You may request to access your Personal Information
  * You may request to rectify your Personal Information
  * You may request to erase your Personal Information
  * You may request for your Personal Information to be ‘forgotten’ by us
  * You may object to the processing of your Personal Information.

To exercise these rights, please contact [privacy@activeconversion.com](mailto:privacy@activeconversion.com). We will respond to your request in a reasonable timeframe and will contact you if we require any further information from you in order to carry out your request.
